Bob Bullock Campaigns papers, Inclusive: 1970-1996, Bulk: 1973-1996
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 1990 Campaign, 1973-1991; 5
  - Elections, 1987-1990; 10
    - Analysis of the 1988 Texas Ballot, circa 1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Endorsements, 1982-1991; 11
    The Endorsements subseries has six sub-subseries: Bob Bullock, Correspondence, Groups, Newspapers, Pending, and Questionnaires. These sub-subseries contain numerous candidate endorsements made by Bullock, correspondence and endorsements of Bob Bullock by individuals, groups, and organizations, clippings of endorsements by newspapers, correspondence on pending endorsements, and questionnaires.
    - Bob Bullock, 1988-1990; 1
      - By Bob Bullock, 1989 February (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Letters of Support, 1988 November (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Letters of Support, 1989 August (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Letters of Support, 1989 September (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Letters of Support, 1989 October (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Letters of Support, 1989 December (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Gifts Sent, 1990 August-December (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Recommendations, 1990 August 1 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Recommendations, 1990 December (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990; 2
      - Correspondence, 1989 July (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1989 September (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, circa 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1990 February (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1990 April (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1990 October 8-17 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1990 October 20-31 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1990 November 1-12 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1990 November 13-21 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - County Chair Letters Project, 1989 September 11 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - County Chair Letters Project, 1989 September 13 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - County Chair Letters Project, 1989 September 14 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - County Chair Letters Project, 1989 September 15 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - County Chair Letters Project, 1989 September 19-28 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - County Chair Letters Project, 1989 October (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - County Chair Letters Project, BL5, 1989 August 4 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - County Chair Letters Project, Mailing Lists, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - County Chair Letters Project, Newest Supporters, 1989 August 4 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - County Chair Letters Project, Undecided, 1989 August 4 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - County Chairman & Coordinators List, circa 1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - County Coordinators Letter Project, 1989 September 6-19, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - County Coordinators Letter Project-List, 1989 September (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - County Coordinators Letter Project-Not Sent, 1989 September 21 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - County Coordinators Letter Project-Thank You Letters, A-G, 1989 September (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - County Coordinators Letter Project-Thank You Letters, H-N, 1989 September (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - County Coordinators Letter Project-Thank You Letters, M-Z, 1989 September (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Final Thank You Letter, 1989 October-November (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Elected Officials List, 1989 September (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1989 June (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1989 July (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1989 September (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1989 October (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1989 November (Box 15, Folder 34)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1990 January (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1990 February (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1990 March (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1990 July (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1990 August (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1990 September (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Endorsing Bullock, 1990 October (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Endorsing Bullock, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Politicians, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Groups, 1982-1990; 3
      - 21 County Coalition, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Aluminum Company of America (ALCOA), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - American Association of Retired Persons, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - American College of Emerging Physicians (Texas Chapter), 1990 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - American Federation of State, County & Municipal Employees, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Angelina County Democratic Voter’s League, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Austin Black Women’s Political Caucus, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Austin Gay/Lesbian Political Caucus, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Austin Progressive Coalition, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Central Labor Council of Webb County, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Clean Water Action, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Combined Law Enforcement Association of Texas, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Community Alliance of Houston, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - County Coordinators Mailing List, 1990 October 8 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Dairy Products Institute of Texas, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Dallas Interdenominational Ministries, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - El Paso Municipal Police Officers Association, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - First Draft List, 1990 February (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Food and Beverage Association of Texas, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Free Enterprise Political Action Committee, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Greater Dallas Association of Realtors, Inc., 1990 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Harris County Democrats, circa 1990 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Harris County Sherriff’s Association, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Houston Baptist Minister’s Association, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Houston Police Officers Association, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Houston Police Patrolmen’s Union, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Houston Lesbian/Gay Political Caucus, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - “IMPACT 2000”, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Lesbian/Gay Democrats of Texas, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Lesbian/Gay Political Coalition of Dallas, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - List (Partial by Organization), 1982; 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Mexican-American Democrats, 1989 December, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Millwrights Local Union #2232, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - National Organization For Women, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Oak Cliff Democrats, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Oak Lawn Democrats, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers Local, #4-23, Port Arthur, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Organization List, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Panhandle Coalition For Choice, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Pipefitters Union #211, Houston, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - San Antonio Professional Firefighters, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Sierra Club, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - State Firemen’s and Fire Marshall’s Association of Texas, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Texas & Southwest Cattleraiser’s Association, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Texas Abortion Rights Action League, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Texas AFL-CIO, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Texas AFL-CIO Firefighters, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Texas Banker’s Association, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Texas Black Publishers, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Texas Coalition of Black Democrats, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Texas Coalition of Black Mayors, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Texas Consumer Association, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Texas Faculty Association, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Texas Farm Bureau & Agfund, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Texas Federation of Teachers, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Texas Hotel/Motel Association, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Texas League of Conservative Voters, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Texas Library Association Political Action Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Texas Public Employees PAC, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Texas Retired Public Employees, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Texas State Rifle Association, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Texas State Teacher’s Association, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Texas Women’s Political Caucus, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Tyler Organization of Men, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - United Farm Workers, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Newspapers, 1987-1990; 4
      - Newspapers, 1987 September (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Newspapers, 1987 November (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Newspapers, 1988 December (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Newspapers, 1989 June (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Newspapers, 1989 September (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Newspapers, 1989 October (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Newspapers, 1990 January (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Newspapers, 1990 February (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Newspapers, 1990 March (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Newspapers, 1990 July (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Newspapers, 1990 September (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Daily Newspaper Editorials, 1990 November (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Daily Newspapers-Primary, 1990 March 13 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Newspaper List, 1987 September, November, 1989 June (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Newspaper List, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Newspaper List, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Pending, 1990-1991; 5
      - Allstate Insurance, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Association of Texas Warehousemen, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Austin Citizens Committee for Fair Immigration, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Business and Professional Women’s Club of Dallas, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Citizens Aware and United to Save the Environment (C.A.U.S.E.), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Dallas Gay Political Caucus, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Disability Political Action Committee, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - DIS-PAC, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Diocese of Fort Worth, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Freedom of Information Foundation of Texas, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Hope Baptist Church, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Individuals: Fonville, James, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - League of Women Voters of Texas Education Fund, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - North Texas NAIOP, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Rosenberg/Richmond Area Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - San Antonio Women’s Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 33)
      - Texas Co-op Power, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 34)
      - Texas Mothers Against Drunk Driving, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 35)
      - Texas Public Citizen, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Texas Tech Student Senate, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Texas United, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Texas Vocational Consortium, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Victims Outreach, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Questionnaires, 1990; 6
      - Association For Retarded Citizens, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Association of Texas Professional Educators, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - American Association of Retired Persons, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Baptist Standard, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - Child Abuse Network, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Common Cause of Texas, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Houston Chronicle, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Houston Defender, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Houston Sun, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Independent Insurance Agents of Texas, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Liberty Coalition, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Midland Reporter-Telegram, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Other Candidates Responses, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Polk County Enterprise, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - The Real Estate Council, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Reference Guides, Inc., 1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Southwest Coalition for Choice, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Texas Alliance for the Mentally Ill, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Texas Association of Private Industry Councils, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Texas Association of School Boards, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Texas Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Texas Junior College Teachers Association, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Texas Public Citizen, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - University of Houston Alumni Organization, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - American Freedom Coalition of Texas, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Campaign Issues Awareness Committee, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Not Answered: Citizens for Excellence in Education, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Not Answered: Environmental Compliance Reporter, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Not Answered: Family Action Coalition of El Paso, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Not Answered: North Texas Arms Rights Coalition, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Not Answered: Meadows Baptist Church, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 25)
      - Not Answered: Tex-Chem PAC, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Not Answered: Texas Eagle Forum, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Not Answered: Texas Fathers Alliance, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Texas Humane Information Network, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Not Answered: Texas Political Report, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Not Answered: Texas Right to Life Committee, Inc., 1990 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Not Answered: Texas United for Life, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Financial, 1973-1991; 12
    The Financial subseries includes four sub-subseries: Card File, Bullock Contribution to Others, General, and Texans for Fundamental Fairness. This subseries contains contribution and expense reports, financial correspondence, contribution letters, and file cards which are arranged alphabetically.
    - Card File, 1973-1988; 1
      - A-F, 1973-1988 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - G-M, 1973-1988 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - N-Z, 1973-1988 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Bullock Contributions to Others, 1987-1991; 2
      - General, 1987 June (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - General, 1987 October (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - General, 1987 November (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - General, 1988 January (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - General, 1988 February (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - General, 1988 June (Box 19, Folder 41)
      - General, 1988 July (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - General, 1988 August (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - General, 1988 September (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - General, 1988 October (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - General, 1988 November (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - General, 1989 January (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - General, 1989 February (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - General, 1989 March (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - General, 1989 May (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - General, 1989 June (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - General, 1989 July (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - General, 1989 July (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - General, 1989 August (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - General, 1989 September (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - General, 1989 October (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - General, 1989 November (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - General, 1989 December (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - General, 1990 January (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - General, 1990 February (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - General, 1990 March (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - General, 1990 May (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - General, 1990 July (Box 20, Folder 22)
      - General, 1990 August (Box 20, Folder 23)
      - General, 1990 September (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - General, 1990 October (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - General, 1991 February (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Bullock Political Contributions List, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - General, 1988-1990; 3
      - Contribution Requests, 1988 May (Box 20, Folder 28)
      - Gifts from Others, 1990 December (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Texans for Fundamental Fairness, 1990; 4
      - Kugle: Contribution Records, 1990 August (Box 20, Folder 30)
      - Kugle: Correspondence, 1990 August (Box 20, Folder 31)
      - Kugle: Handwritten Notes, circa 1990 August (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Invitations, 1987-1990; 13
    Invitations includes two sub-subseries: Fundraisers and General. Invitations reflect fundraising and campaign events for Bullock and the Democratic Party Convention. They include actual invitations and pledge cards.
    - Fundraisers, 1987-1990; 1
      - Cypress Valley Skeet Shoot (“On Target With Bob Bullock”), 1987 October 3 (Box 20, Folder 33)
      - “A Special Evening With Bob Bullock”, 1988 December 1 (Box 20, Folder 34)
      - “A Special Texas Evening With Bob Bullock”, 1989 December 6 (Box 20, Folder 35)
      - “A Special Evening With Bob Bullock”, 1990 September 11 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - General, 1990; 2
      - Democratic Party Convention: Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Democratic Party Convention: Correspondence, 1990 April (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Party Convention: Correspondence, 1990 May (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Democratic Party Convention: Correspondence, 1990 June (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Democratic Party, County Chairman: Correspondence, 1990 October 10-12 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Issues, 1979-1991; 14
    The Issues subseries has seven sub-subseries: General, Blacks, Emerging, Environment, Gay/Lesbian, Hispanics, Labor, and Other. Issues reflects correspondence and research, as well as news clippings, articles, and reports on the pertinent political issues of each campaign. Bullock conducted extensive and thorough research into any issue that currently existed or that he felt might grow to importance during his campaigns. The 1990 Campaign series contains the most extensive portion of issue files.
    - General, 1987; 1
      - Holiday Open House, Bullock Campaign Office, 1987 December 16 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Blacks, 1988-1990; 2
      - Advertising, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1989 September (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1990 January (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1990 February (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1990 May (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1990 July (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1990 October (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 1990 November (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Mailing Lists, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Mailing Lists, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Mailing Lists, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Mailing Lists, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - News Clippings, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Publications, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Emerging, 1990; 3
      - Corrections, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Environmental Protection, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Fuel Tax, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Other, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - Public Education Finance, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Transportation, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Environment, 1990; 4
      - Article, 1990 January (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence, 1990 January (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1990 February (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990 February (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1990 April (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1990 May (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1990 June (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1990 July (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1990 August (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1990 October (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - News Clippings, 1990 March (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - News Clippings, 1990 April (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Flyers, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Gay/Lesbian, 1988-1991; 5
      - Article, 1989 November (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 1988 February (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1988 July (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, 1989 June (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, 1989 September (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, circa 1989 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 1990 January (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, 1990 February (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1990 April (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 1990 May (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1990 October (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 1990 December (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 1991 January (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - News Clippings, 1990 April (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - News Clippings, 1991 June (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Newsletters, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Publications, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Publications, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Hispanics, 1987-1990; 6
      - Advertising, circa 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1987 October (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1989 February (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1989 May (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1989 September (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, 1990 May (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1990 June (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1990 July (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1990 August (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, 1990 October (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, 1990 November (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, circa 1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - News Clippings, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Publications, 1990 September (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Labor, 1979-1991; 7
      - AFL-CIO Convention Speech, 1979 July (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 1989 September (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, 1990 January (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Correspondence, 1990 February (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Correspondence, 1990 April (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Correspondence, 1990 June (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Correspondence, 1990 July (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence, 1990 August (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1990 October (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1990 November (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - News Clippings, 1989 September (Box 24, Folder 4)